mmaplayground.com 2017-06-06

# MMAPlayground.com Privacy Policy

|   
  
---|---  
  
Effective: March 26, 2014 

If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, including the use of your personally identifiable information in any manner described here, you may be prohibited from using much of our websites and services, including revocation of your membership. MMAPlayground may update this Privacy Policy from time-to-time in our sole discretion. In such case, MMAPlayground will attempt to provide you with notice to the email address on file for your account, no less than 30 days prior to any such update. It is your responsibility to check your email for updates, and to review the Privacy Policy for any changes. You agree that each time that you use the Site and Services and you are bound by any such changes. Use of the Site and Services by you following us emailing you or posting a new privacy policy on our Site constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy Policy as modified. 

**What information do we collect?**

**Registration information** \- When you sign up for the Site, we ask for your personal information. In some cases, we may also ask you to send us additional information or to answer additional questions to help verify your information. 

**Information obtained from third parties** \- We may obtain information about you from third parties to verify the information you provide. We also may obtain information from third parties in connection with providing the Services to you. 

**Submission information** – When you submit information through the Services, we may store that information and also collect and store metadata about that information. We do not screen for personally identifying information; to the extent you have included any such information in your submissions, it will be stored and disclosed in the course of our general use of such information. 

**Information about your use of the service** \- We may collect information about your interaction with the service to help validate your identity or detect potentially fraudulent conduct. 

**User-provided contact information** – MMAPlayground may track and/or gather emails of visitors that contact and/or communicate with MMAPlayground. 

**Cookies** \- When you access an MMAPlayground web page, we may send one or more cookies (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). 

**Log information** \- When you use the Site, our servers may automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. User inputted Site search data may be recorded and stored for research purposes and/or to help resolve possible technical issues which may in turn link a user ID to the performed search. 

**User communications** \- When you send an email or other communication to us or other Site users. 

**Links** \- We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. 

**What do we use your information for?**

**To personalize your experience** – Your information helps us better respond to and tailor our Site and Services to your individual needs. 

**To improve our Site** – we continually update and improve our website and Services based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 

**To improve customer service**

**To process transactions for Fight Points (as defined in the Terms of Use)**

**To administer promotions, surveys or other Site features**

**To send you periodic emails** – the email address you provide for registration purposes may be used to send you information about this website, in addition to occasional news, updates, related product or service information (including, but not limited to sharing such non-specific information with third parties), etc. Users may opt out of receiving emails from MMAPlayground concerning upcoming events and Site announcements by clicking the corresponding "unsubscribe" link found in each and every communication sent from MMAPlayground. 

We will not disclose or sell personally identifiable data to third parties, except as necessary to provide the services. You understand and agree that MMAPlayground may use non-personally identifying data and aggregate data in connection with the above and may share or sell such data to third parties. If you do not want your non-personally identifying data shared, you may write to us. You understand and agree that any decision you make to withhold any information from MMAPlayground may prevent MMAPlayground from being able to fulfill your request and/or impair your ability to utilize all functionality of the Site. 

**How do we protect your information?**

MMAPlayground has implemented various security features to help prevent any unauthorized release of personal information. Our features include technical and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. Be advised that while MMAPlayground has endeavored to make a secure reliable Site for its users, the privacy and confidentiality of communications transmitted to/from MMAPlayground via this Site or through email cannot be guaranteed. As such, MMAPlayground is not held responsible for the security of any data transmitted via the Internet to/from our website. 

The security of your account also depends on keeping your account password confidential and you should not share your account name or password with anyone. If you do share your account information with a third party, they will have access to your account and your personal information. 

**Accessing and Editing Your Personal Information**

You have the ability to access and edit any personal information held on the site. You may do so by logging into your profile and changing any user information stored on file there. To the extent that such information is stored in our databases, we will respond to your changes as soon as reasonably possible. Please note that although you may delete this information from your profile, the information may remain stored indefinitely in our backup and archival records. While your personal information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our Site. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**Age Restrictions**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), as we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any personal information through the Site. 

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date. 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through the Site or write to us at 67 Harned Rd. Suite 2B, Commack, NY 11725.
